&l &l
(heartbeat thumping)
(heartbeat grows louder)
(heartbeat fades)
(switch clicks)
PATSY CLINE (on CD):
&l I fall &l
&l To pieces &l
PATSY CLINE (on CD):
&l I fall &l
&l Each time I see you again... &l
&l To pieces... &l
(woman yelling, grunting)
(man grunts)
(screaming)
You have the wrong girl!
My name is Bridget
and I'm an addict.
GROUP:
Hi, Bridget.
I've been sober for six months.
Which is longer than some of the
relationships that I've had.
(gentle laughter)
Things have been tense.
It's been really hard
to stay clean.
But I am.
I finally got a response
from my sister Siobhan.
She wants me to come visit,
stay as long as I want.
I'm not sure I'm ready for that.
For family, I mean.
I'm okay, but I'm not that okay.
(gentle laughter)
I just keep reminding myself--
mistakes aren't tragedies, but:
ALL: Please, Higher Power,
help me learn from them.
mistakes aren't tragedies, but:
Shouldn't drink
that so late.
You're gonna
have trouble sleeping.
Mm. I have trouble with
or without the coffee.
(sighs)
Give me that.
Oh... now you want my cookies.
I should probably go.
My guy's waiting.
Are you sure you don't want me
there tomorrow?
I'm sure.
Is that your boyfriend
or sponsor?
Malcolm?
Sponsor, but...
Sponsor.
Here, Jimmy, I figured
you could use it.
Thanks, hon.
Anything for you.
Uh... pick you up 7:30.
We're not having a sleepover?
If you need anything...
I know.
Jimmy's got my back.
You okay?
Not really.
Just get up on the stand, you
tell the judge what you saw.
You were a witness
to a crime.
You did nothing
wrong, okay?
It'll be over before
you know it.
That's what I'm afraid of.
Bridget... we'll protect you.
You don't get it.
If Bodaway
wants me dead, I'm dead.
No one can protect me.
If Bodaway
wants me dead, I'm dead.
ANCHORMAN: In other news,
tomorrow begins the trial
of Wind River Reservation
crime boss Bodaway Macawi.
In 2009, Macawi was accused
but eventually acquitted
of the murder of a...
(changing channel)
ANCHORMAN:
Macawi is being indicted
for the dismemberment killing
of Shaylene Briggs,
a dancer in his Rock Springs
strip club.
(turns off TV)
Jimmy!
Bridget!
That crazy bitch took my gun.
(rock music playing
in background)
(bus horn honks twice)
Excuse me! Miss!
Forgot your wallet.
Thank you.
Is that all you brought?
Traveling light these days.
(sighs)
I was wondering how you'd look
after six years.
Not nearly as good as you.
Come here.
I missed you so much.
This is our weekend place.
Make yourself at home.
Looks just like my house.
Except not at all.
Your life
seems perfect.
Close to it.
But no one's life
is perfect.
So... it's just the two
of us this weekend.
Where's Andrew?
He's in London. Working.
Then visiting Juliet
at boarding school.
So... how long have
you guys been married?
Almost five years.
Bridget, listen...
Andrew doesn't
exactly know about you.
About my visiting?
He doesn't know
I have a sister.
&l How can it be
that every time &l
&l I've lost myself
and I've gone out of line &l
&l You're there &l
&l And why is it that,
when I'm such a wreck &l
&l I look at the life
that I want to forget &l
&l You remind me I'm okay... &l
I want you to know...
how sorry I am...
for everything.
You already apologized
in your letter.
I know, it's just...
making amends is...
Step number nine.
I did my research.
&l You see right through
my flaws... &l
I think about Sean every day.
I don't want
to talk about it.
I think about Sean every day.
Will you just hear me out?
Because of what I did...
Bridget, stop.
You're already forgiven.
You just need to forgive
yourself.
&l And how do you know,
when nothing is clear &l
&l The right things to say
so I can heal &l
&l And face another day... &l
&l The right things to say
so I can heal &l
Well, what was your
relationship like
with Bridget Kelly?
MALCOLM: That's one of the
problems with being a sponsor--
you get close.
How close?
Let's just say
I regretted it.
How close?
Do you love her?
That's none of your business.
I find it hard to believe that
Bridget would disappear
without contacting you.
Well, she hasn't...
and I'm really worried.
Well, you should be.
Because, without her testimony,
Bodaway's a free man.
Well, you should be.
The guy's ruthless.
He killed his own brother.
Better hope I find
her before he does.
&l Time, it cuts you
to the bone... &l
BRIDGET:
This reminds me of Tahoe.
SIOBHAN: Why do you think
I love it out here?
I'm gonna get us some drinks.
&l Is my heart, is my soul... &l
So...
are you still, um...
dancing?
So...
You mean stripping?
Nah.
But I still work for tips.
Waitressing.
Um...
I don't want to be the sister
you have to pretend
doesn't exist.
Just so you know...
I missed you, too.
&l Fall awake, neverest &l
&l We neverest... &l
(song fades)
(gulls keening, squawking)
How long was I out for?
Siobhan?
Siobhan?!
Siobhan!
Oh, my God.
(radio static)
Hello?
Hello?! Hello?!
(radio static)
It's my sister.
Can anyone hear me? Hello?
(gasping)
Siobhan!
Siobhan! Siobhan!
Evening, Mrs. Martin.
Evening.
Hope you enjoyed
the Hamptons.
&l &l
(elevator bell dings)
&l Pages turning,
lights are burning &l
(elevator bell dings)
&l See what you could not see &l
&l You gotta believe
that this all leads &l
&l See what you could not see &l
&l To somewhere
we've never been &l
&l We won't run, we can fight &l
&l All that keeps us up
at night &l
&l There is far to go now... &l
(door closes)
MAN:
Shiv?
Siobhan?
(door closes)
MAN:
Shiv?
Hi.
Well, aren't you friendly?
It's been forever.
Two weeks is hardly forever.
Have you lost weight?
Maybe a little.
Hmm, you're too thin.
So, how was London?
Cold. But I did get
that investor on board.
Congratulations.
You're being sarcastic?
No.
Oh, I've got
something for you.
The maid said you're
using a new cleaners.
Oh, I've got
something for you.
I'll take them in the morning.
Oh, and that e-mail you
sent about the ballet?
I really don't want
to go.
Okay.
That was easy.
I'm gonna take a shower.
(shivering)
MALCOLM:
Hello.
I can't believe what I've done.
Bridget?!
Where the hell are you?
I didn't think I had a choice.
What are you talking about?
What did you do?!
Siobhan killed herself.
&l Waiting for the break
of day &l
Siobhan killed herself.
I don't know why she did it.
&l Searching for something
to say &l
I don't know why she did it.
I'm the only one
that knows that she's dead.
&l Flashing lights against
the sky &l
I saw a way out
and I took it.
&l Giving up, I close my eyes &l
I was so scared.
&l Should I try
to do some more? &l
I was so scared.
The cops were after me.
Bodaway was after me.
&l 25 or six to four &l
I felt like I didn't have
a choice.
&l 25 or six to four &l
It was so easy, Malcolm.
&l Feeling like I ought
to sleep &l
It was so easy, Malcolm.
I mean, they all think
that I'm her.
&l Spinning room
is sinking deep &l
They all think I'm Siobhan.
They're looking for you.
Tell me where you are
and I'll come and get you.
No, it's not safe
for either of us.
I shouldn't have even
called you.
&l 25 or six to four &l
Bridget?! Bridget?!
I gotta go.
Bridget, wait...
&l Should I try
to do some more? &l
&l 25 or six to four. &l
(water running)
(water stops)
(phone ringing)
Are you gonna
get that?
(ringing continues)
Are you gonna
get that?
Hello?
WOMAN:
Hey, gorgeous! Where are you?!
Hello?
You were supposed to meet me
at the loft half an hour ago.
I was?
Don't tell me you didn't know.
I saw you write it
in your little orange book.
Don't tell me you didn't know.
Why were you
still in bed?
If you skipped
your trainer
because I said you were
too thin, that's just silly.
Siobhan, darling,
did you fall back asleep?
because I said you were
too thin, that's just silly.
No, Gemma.
Um, I'll be there.
Can you just give me 20 minutes?
No, Gemma.
Make it 30.
Now you owe me a latte.
(grinder rasping,
rock music playing)
You look absolutely
anorexic.
You must share your secret.
Good news.
Got the marble people coming
in at 10:00 instead of 4:00.
The lighting guy can
make it after lunch.
What do you think of
the exposed brick?
It's great.
Told you it would be.
Just one question.
Why are we moving again?
Ask your crazy husband.
It took me a year and a half
to finish Park Avenue,
and now he wants to start over.
But it's the penthouse.
(gasps)
Come see the terrace.
But it's the penthouse.
So?
It's pretty.
You don't seem
that excited.
What's wrong?
I thought you lived
for this stuff.
I do.
I'm just tired.
Andrew came home
late last night.
I'm just tired.
You're skinny
and you're having sex?
No, we didn't.
The last time I saw Henry
naked was right before
the twins turned three
last year.
I think Henry's having
an affair.
I can't stand
to look at him,
let alone sleep
next to him.
Oh, I could so use you
and a martini.
Say you'll go out with me
tonight.
I would love to.
Oh, no, wait.
Don't you have that thing?
What thing?
The fund-raising thing?
Yes! I totally forgot.
I'll be fine.
I'll just hook up
with one of the workmen.
I'll be fine.
I'm sure contractors
make more money
than out-of-work novelists.
I'm sure contractors
make more money
(woman singing aria)
(singing fades out)
(singing fades in)
(aria ends, applause)
Hey, Jim.
Andrew.
Hey, you know,
it's been years
since you've worn
that dress.
Is it too much?
No, it's absolutely
perfect.
Now, a glass
of champagne?
Actually, could you make
mine water?
I have a little bit
of a headache.
Absolutely.
(gasps)
What the hell are you doing?!
I just wanted to show you
how much I missed you.
Gemma said you were
gonna be here tonight.
Henry?
Relax. Andrew
can't see us.
Henry?
This is too much.
No, what's too much is
I haven't seen you in a week.
So you got detained
in the Hamptons. Fine.
I haven't seen you in a week.
But then when
you didn't
show up at the hotel,
I went to your place,
and you just stared at me
from the balcony
like I was some kind
of crazy person.
And now this.
I have to go.
No, no.
Not until you tell me
what's going on.
No, no.
We can't do this here.
Andrew's waiting
for me.
We can't do this here.
Like you care.
Let him wait.
Henry, please.
Fine. Meet me at the hotel
on Thursday.
The nanny is taking the boys
to the park at noon.
Um, uh, noon...
I could be late. Traffic
from the new apartment.
Um, uh, noon...
The apartment is two minutes
away from the Dandridge.
You're making me
nervous, Siobhan.
You won't even
look at me.
Hey, I want to see you.
Okay.
I-I'll meet you there.
Nothing has changed on my end.
My hook is stuck.
Do you mind?
Is everything okay?
Fine.
It just... I thought...
You thought what?
I don't know,
that we were cool?
Cool? What are we, 12?
I don't know,
that we were cool?
Of course we're not cool.
But tonight at the gala,
you-you seemed so happy.
That was an act.
This is your game,
Siobhan.
That was an act.
I'm just playing
by the rules.
What if I don't want
to play games anymore?
Well, that would be a first.
I'm serious.
Why can't we just be nice
to each other, for real?
Who are you?
Why can't we just be nice
to each other, for real?
What do you mean?
You're just so different.
Just relaxed
and agreeable.
And you don't like it?
No.
I love it.
I just don't believe it.
(sniffs)
(sighs)
Mistakes aren't tragedies.
But please, Higher Power...
GROUP:
...help me learn from them.
This is the hardest thing
I've ever had to do,
but right now, it's
the only choice that I have.
Sobriety is
the only choice.
but right now, it's
the only choice that I have.
I feel like every time
I clean up a mess,
I end up dirty.
(sniffs)
I never meant
for any of this to happen.
(sniffs)
It just did.
The important
thing
It just did.
is for you to take
responsibility for your actions.
In all this,
I lost someone
who meant everything to me.
I just got her back.
Now she's gone.
(sniffs)
Maybe once things settle down,
I can go back to my old life,
(elevator bell dings)
be normal again.
Maybe once things settle down,
I can go back to my old life,
But for now...
WOMAN:
Hey.
But for now...
(man and woman
laughing)
Andrew?
(woman laughing)
(man and woman laughing)
(rock music playing)
Juliet?
What the hell, Siobhan!
Don't you knock?!
What's going on?
Wait, is that my scarf?
Send me the dry cleaning bill.
Did you go through my drawers?
Will you just leave already?
I'll text you.
Thanks a lot, Siobhan.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you
were coming home.
It's my house. I can
stop by any time I want.
I didn't know you
were coming home.
Of course you can. I just...
I wasn't expecting you.
I shouldn't have to be
at boarding school anyway.
The only reason that Daddy
sent me was because of you.
Juliet, I'm not trying
to start a fight.
Since when?
(phone ringing)
Hello.
Yeah, whatever.
Some guy is coming up
to see you.
Who?
Juliet, did they say who?
(sighs)
(elevator bell dings)
Juliet, did they say who?
Wow.
Far cry
from Wyoming.
Wow.
You ever been?
My name's Victor Machado.
I'm with the FBI.
Siobhan Martin.
How can I help you?
I'm here to talk to you
about your sister.
Can I buy you
a cup of coffee?
I'm here to talk to you
about your sister.
So you really have no idea
where your sister is?
Not a clue.
Well, then I'm guessing
you don't know what kind
of trouble she's in.
Well, then I'm guessing
Well, I assume you didn't
come all the way out here
because she was jaywalking.
(chuckles)
That's amazing.
The same pretty face,
the same sarcastic
attitude.
The same pretty face,
I'm sorry.
I'm just not exactly sure
what this has to do with me.
I'm sorry.
My sister and I
are not close.
We haven't spoken in years.
Bridget's a fugitive.
She assaulted a police officer
and she stole his weapon.
Bridget's a fugitive.
Bridget wouldn't do that.
You sound pretty confident,
and yet you're not close.
Bridget wouldn't do that.
We're twins.
Bridget was the only
eyewitness to a murder.
She'd been arrested
for prostitution and possession.
We agreed to drop those charges
if she'd testify.
But that never happened.
We're very concerned
for her safety.
But that never happened.
If she didn't talk,
why are you so concerned?
Because the man she was supposed
to testify against is now free
and he's going to make sure
he doesn't go back to prison.
Silencing your sister
is his only insurance.
Mrs. Martin,
if you know something,
anything, you need to tell me.
She's facing arrest.
Or worse.
The bottom line--
she's not going
to get far either way.
The bottom line--
&l &l
(sighs)
Siobhan?
You scared me.
What are you doing here?
I thought I would check
on the progress.
At 9:00?
I was in the area.
Huh.
Well, I was going
to surprise you,
but since you're
already here,
won't this look amazing
on that wall over a black
lacquered console table?
won't this look amazing
Don't worry, those holes
will be covered by tomorrow.
Perfect.
You know, if it weren't
for this pain-in-the-ass
renovation, I'd be obsessing
over who Henry's
having an affair with.
Why else do you
think I'm here
at 9:00 at night?
At least you have a
sense of humor about it.
at 9:00 at night?
Hmm.
Do you have any idea
who it might be?
Hmm.
Well, I went through
the list of usual suspects,
but the trainer's gay,
the maid's fat,
the wife's best friend...
I'm joking.
Come on, you're
so not his type.
I'm joking.
(nervous chuckle)
(knocking on door)
I'm not here to
sleep with you.
Why? I'm here
to sleep with you.
Henry, you're my
best friend's husband.
That never bothered
you before.
Well, it does now.
I don't get it.
What is it, Siobhan?
Gemma's on to us.
She told me that she thinks
you're cheating on her.
With who?
I suggested the nanny.
Annafried's
a lesbian.
I suggested the nanny.
Yeah, well, I really
couldn't think of what
else to say at the moment.
Annafried's
a lesbian.
How about,
Henry is a great guy,
and he would never cheat on you?
We just need to
lay low for a while.
I've been trying
to lay low.
I'm serious.
We just need to
lay low for a while.
If you really love me,
you'll stay away.
ANDREW:
This is the third time.
I keep letting you get away
with this crap, but I'm done.
Daddy, please, you don't
know what happened...
No. You could have gone to jail.
And did you ever stop
to think for one second
No. You could have gone to jail.
how your behavior is
affecting this family?
What family?
Siobhan hates me.
And you're never around.
I'm going to Mom's.
You know that's
not an option.
I'm going to Mom's.
Great, Daddy.
Just throw it in my face that
she doesn't want me, either.
Great, Daddy.
Juliet, that's not what I meant.
Juliet.
What's going on?
Nothing.
(cell phone ringing)
Hello.
MAN:
Mrs. Martin, this is Dr. Marx.
Sorry to call so late,
but you didn't show up
for your appointment
this afternoon.
I'm sorry.
I, um, I must've forgotten
to write it in my book.
Well, reschedule when you can,
because your blood work
came back positive.
Oh, is that a bad thing?
No, a great thing.
Congratulations.
You're about four weeks along.
I-I'm pregnant?
(sighs softly)
Siobhan, what did you do?
GEMMA:
Pregnant?
(sighs softly)
You sneaky bitch!
So that's why
you haven't been drinking.
You sneaky bitch!
Isn't that
great, Henry?
Great.
Isn't that
great, Henry?
Great.
Oh, he's just upset
'cause his editor
doesn't like
his new pages.
HENRY:
Thank you for sharing that.
What? Don't let
your bad mood
get in the way of
their good news.
What? Don't let
your bad mood
Congratulations.
Thank you.
We're both
very happy.
Well, I could use a refill.
Henry.
Uh, no, thanks.
Step this way.
I'm buying.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want it
to come out that way.
You know
that's my baby.
No, I don't.
Oh, come on, Siobhan.
We've slept together
a thousand times,
and you've thrown
Andrew a bone,
what, once, twice in
the past few months?
That is my kid.
And I'm not just
going to smile
and pretend to be
happy for Andrew.
What do you want me to do?
Leave him.
I can't.
If you don't leave
him, we're over.
Make a choice.
Him or me.
I choose him.
ANDREW:
I know we negotiated that.
But I want out.
Look, the, uh, wife
just walked in.
We'll finish
this later.
Look, the, uh, wife
just walked in.
Do you think Henry was
acting strange last night?
You know
those artist types.
They're temperamental.
What about Juliet?
I mean, she seemed pretty upset.
You both did.
She got kicked out
of boarding school.
For what?
She got kicked out
of boarding school.
You're kidding me.
Tell me about it.
Well, she can't stay here.
Not with the baby coming.
Come on, Shiv.
She's got nowhere else to go.
So you found them breaking into
the bus station lockers?
Four kids, easy target.
Didn't think much of it,
till we found this.
Looks like your girl's
been here.
Her sister Siobhan said
they hadn't spoken in years.
Wonder what else
she's lying about.
Her sister Siobhan said
they hadn't spoken in years.
(cell phone beeping)
GEMMA:
It's Gemma.
Meet me at the loft in an hour.
I think I know who Henry's
having an affair with.
Meet me at the loft in an hour.
Gemma?
&l &l
PATSY CLINE (on CD):
&l I fall &l
&l To pieces &l
&l Each time I see you again &l
&l I fall... &l
(grunting)
You have the wrong girl!
(panting)
(groaning)
I'm not Bridget.
(groaning weakly)
Siobhan.
(phone ringing)
(phone continues ringing)
Hello?
MAN:
Siobhan, we have a problem.
Hello?
Captioning sponsored by
CBS
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Captioning sponsored by
CBS